Hi and welcome to a video on my channel Cillian Nox. I'm presenting you today a new location and
I brought something special. Designer role play lingerie from Bad Stories from Ukraine. The sets
come in these neat little boxes and I'm going to unpack one. I have four sets I want to show you.
The whole superhero collection so super lady spider lady and bat lady and a set called gift
and the aim is to allow women to transform and oh this is the red one I
didn't know which one I was going to unpack so this is the one called gift
and I think I'll change into the first one right away which I have to find
first I'm going to start with the bat lady and I didn't promise you too much
because there's a cape and really cool bra so this is really special lingerie
and I can't wait to change now the bat lady how cool is that I love the cape
and I also love the suspender belt yeah the penny and bra I think it's a really
I have to turn around.
I think the concept of this kind of role-playing lingerie is really unique because it's really
high quality and you can really tell that there went some thought into the designs and
what you can do with the separate parts already.
So it's not just some cheap costume, I think it's really classy.
I love the combination of black and gold and the cape is detachable.
So if you like it a bit more toned down and are not a fan of capes, you can remove it.
And yeah, you can play by your own rules with this kind of lingerie.
I'm going to search for the second outfit and I think I'll do the super lady now.
This is the whole set and since this location has so many cool spots, I'm going to go upstairs
now.
Upstairs!
The super lady set.
It's got a belt again, a panty and a bra.
this time the cape is attached to the bra and it has kind of a more yeah more
closed look so with the almost top part here maybe you can wear this for
Halloween who knows up to you since I'm super lady unfortunately I cannot fly
But its location makes me almost believe that I can fly.
The Spider Lady, this is the last
of the three superhero outfits.
And it is very, very see-through,
that's why I'm wearing pasties and stuff.
And also, if you have a look at the product picture here,
you can see the whole outfit
because there's a mask integrated in the bra,
which I'm not going to wear yet
because I want to talk to you, obviously.
I'm showing you later though.
And the garter belt is integrated with the panties.
So this is one piece here,
which is really cute with the boning here
and then it kind of stands away like a spider web.
And also the bra part with the hood is separate.
a separate so this is the only two-piece set yeah nevertheless it's a cool look I
added some stockings again and now I'm trying to put on the hood this is a fun
look I can talk no problem because it's a bit loose here and it's a bit short
here in the neck area so I can't really put the head up or move it too far to any side.
But yeah it's definitely a cool look also for taking pictures which I'll do in a second.
It's definitely a lot so either have to love it or don't. I like it.
This is definitely the most extravagant look of the four of them. You're not used to
seeing hoods here on this channel, so this is a first. Enjoy it. It's kind of lingerie. Cool,
cool. Yeah, I don't know. Whoever thought of this, well done. A special of this location are this
height adjustable light thing and I'm going to take some pictures with them now because I think
it's a cool look together. Last outfit for today it's called Gift because there's a bow in the back
and a lot of frills and it looks just so cute. I bought stockings for this outfit especially for
this one because I don't have red ones and I found these cool ones with a red line in the back.
I think this is an awesome look and I like the overall outfit.
You have to like all the frills and all the cuteness but as much as I'm not a girly, as
much as I like this one anyway, I don't know.
It's nice.
Okay, these were the four outfits I wanted to show you today.
Check out Bad Stories, they're from Ukraine.
You can support them by shopping there.
ship worldwide which is really cool and they have a lot more cool outfits you can find on their
homepage i'll link everything down below and also let me know which of the outfits was your favorite
one it's hard for me i think the bad girl because i like bats and i'm a goth so it's kind of obvious
but i think supergirl was also fun they are really cool and i think these make great gifts
which is why it's called gift maybe no um yeah anyway you see you in the next video bye